# WAN FARAH ZAHIDAH BINTI SABARUDIN



9504200075826



012-6073584



382, Jalan Bagan Ajam, 13000, Butterworth, Penang



wanfaraz@gmail.com



I am dedicated and fast leaner. I am looking forward to experience the challenging and competitive environment. I am a good team player that can that can work with people from different background and help the company to achieve the goals.



### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

**2015-2017** 

**Bachelor of Arts (Hons)** 

**English Language Studies** 

Current CGPA: 3.09

• 2013-2014

Universiti Teknologi Mara

Foundation of Law

**CGPA: 3.08** 

2011-2012

Sekolah Menengah Vokasional

Sungai Petani 2

Sijil Peperiksaan Malaysia (SPM)

Result: 2A+3A3A-



### **WORKING EXPERIENCES**

**2012-2013** 

Soft Soya Carnival Mall (Supervisor)

**2015-2017** 

Ifarahya Enterprise

(Part Timer - Shop Assistant)

- **2016-2017**
- · Sabrina Tuition Centre

(Part Time Tutor)

- **2017**
- Stradford International College (Internship in Marketing)

# **EXTRA CURRICULAR**ACTIVITIES

#### 2015-2017

- Persatuan Mahasiswa Pulau Pinang (EXCO Public Relations)
- Procitra 17(Marketing and Sponsorship Members)
- Kem Kembara Pemimpin(EXCO Protocol)
- Kem Adik Sukses (KEMAS)(Facilitator)
- ➤ WeCare Darul Hanan (Facilitator)
- Unit Protokol Kolej Keris Mas (EXCO TTK)
- Karnival Konvokesyen UKM 46 (EXCO Protocol)
- Kursus Protokol dan Etiket Sosial (EXCO Publisity and Media)
- ➤ Best Student SPM 2012 Awards
- Perakaunan
- · Sejarah

### PERSONAL SKILLS

Microsoft Word

Microsoft PowerPoint

**Microsoft Publisher** 

Microsoft Excel

Movie Maker

Adobe Photoshop



## A LANGUAGES

- ✓ Bahasa Malaysia
- ✓ English



- ❖ Prof Madya Dr Pramela Krish A/P
- N. Krishnasamy

pramela@ukm.edu.my

03-89216496

Dr Kemboja binti Ismail

oja@pkrisc.cc.ukm.my

0389216472

❖ Siti Nor binti Ishak

019-5740735/013-4715332